Guide to the Popular music poster collection, 1970-2006.
Popular music poster collection, 1970-2006.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Popular music poster collection, 1970-2006.
8100
Thomas, Hill
141 mapcase folders.
Printed materials, posters.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Promotional posters for pop and rock music bands printed in England, Germany, Denmark, and other European countries, 1970s-2006.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Promotional posters for pop and rock music bands printed in England, Germany, Denmark, and other European countries, 1970s-2006.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Hill, Thomas,
Subjects:
Popular music; Rock music; Electronic music; Electronic music; Popular music; Rock music
Form and Genre Terms:
Posters.; Posters
INFORMATION FOR USERS
SERIES LIST
Series I. Alphabetical Order
Series II. By Location
Series III. By Music Genre
Series IV. Other
CONTAINER LIST
- Alphabetical Order, 1970-2006
  - A1-Am posters, 1970-2006 (Folder 1)
  - An-Az posters, 1970-2006 (Folder 2)
  - Ba-Bm posters, 1970-2006 (Folder 3-4)
  - Bn-Bz posters, 1970-2006 (Folder 5)
  - Ca-Cm posters, 1970-2006 (Folder 6)
  - Cn-Cz posters, 1970-2006 (Folder 7)
  - Da-Dm posters, 1970-2006 (Folder 8-9)
  - Dn-D4 posters, 1970-2006 (Folder 10)
  - Ea-Em posters, 1970-2006 (Folder 11)
  - En-Ez posters, 1970-2006 (Folder 12)
  - Fa-Fm posters, 1970-2006 (Folder 13)
  - Fn-Fz posters, 1970-2006 (Folder 14)
  - G-Gm posters, 1970-2006 (Folder 15)
  - Gn-Gz posters, 1970-2006 (Folder 16)
  - H-Hm posters, 1970-2006 (Folder 17)
  - Hanson and Hendrix posters, 1970-2006 (Folder 18)
  - Hn-Hz posters, 1970-2006 (Folder 19)
  - I posters, 1970-2006 (Folder 20)
  - Ja-Jm posters, 1970-2006 (Folder 21)
  - Jn-Jz posters, 1970-2006 (Folder 22)
  - Ka-Km posters, 1970-2006 (Folder 23)
  - Kn-Kz posters, 1970-2006 (Folder 24)
  - L-Lm posters, 1970-2006 (Folder 25-26)
  - Ln-Lz posters, 1970-2006 (Folder 27)
  - Ma-Mm posters, 1970-2006 (Folder 28-29)
  - Marley and Metallica posters, 1970-2006 (Folder 30)
  - Mn-Mz posters, 1970-2006 (Folder 31)
  - N-Nm posters, 1970-2006 (Folder 32)
  - Nn-Nz posters, 1970-2006 (Folder 33)
  - O-Om posters, 1970-2006 (Folder 34)
  - On-Oz posters, 1970-2006 (Folder 35)
  - P-Pm posters, 1970-2006 (Folder 36)
  - Pn-Pz posters, 1970-2006 (Folder 37)
  - Q posters, 1970-2006 (Folder 38)
  - Ra-Rm posters, 1970-2006 (Folder 39-40)
  - Rn-Rz posters, 1970-2006 (Folder 41)
  - S-Sm posters, 1970-2006 (Folder 42)
  - Sn-Sz posters, 1970-2006 (Folder 43-44)
  - T-Tm posters, 1970-2006 (Folder 45)
  - Tn-Tz posters, 1970-2006 (Folder 46)
  - U posters, 1970-2006 (Folder 47)
  - V posters, 1970-2006 (Folder 48)
  - WXYZ posters, 1970-2006 (Folder 49)
  - Multiple Artists posters, 1970-2006 (Folder 50)
  - Number posters, 1970-2006 (Folder 51)
  - Duplicate music posters, 1970-2006 (Folder 123)
- By Location, 1970-2006
  - German, 1970-2006
    - Concert/Event posters in German, 1970-2006 (Folder 53-75)
    - Concert/Event posters in German, 1970-2006 (Folder 94-102)
    - Concerts in Germany posters, 1970-2006 (Folder 60-62)
      Germany
    - Events/Shows in Germany posters, 1970-2006 (Folder 83)
    - Pop, Rock concerts in Germany posters, 2005-2006 (Folder 84-85)
  - Other, 1970-2006
    - Denmark Rock, Pop, Underground posters, 1970-1990 (Folder 76-79)
      Note: "In and around Freestate Christiania"
      Denmark
    - Pop, Rock concerts & album release in Austria, 2000-2006 (Folder 81-82)
      Rolling Stones, Shakira, Rammstein, Phil Collins, Rod Stewart, Kylie Minogue, Nina Hagen, Sting, Iggy Pop, Bon Jovi, Eric Clapton, Billy Joel, etc.
      Austria
  - Multiple Locations, 1970-2006
    - Punk concert posters, 1970-2006 (Folder 80)
      Mostly in San Francisco, some in Germany & Austria
      San Francisco, California
    - Punk concert posters, 1970-2006 (Folder 121)
    - European punk concert posters, 1970-2006 (Folder 92-93)
      Package included note: "It's hardcore-punk baby! / Koterkacke - Kiezpunk F-Hain / Stalinstadt Ensemble - Zonen-HC Punk-Brigade Schuttstadt / Sax and Violins - Aparte 80's hits cover Tanzkapelle DD"
- By Music Genre, 1970-2006
  - Pop, Rock posters, 1970-1990 (Folder 52)
  - Pop, Rock posters, 1970-1990 (Folder 120)
  - Punk music posters, 1970-2006 (Folder 86-87)
  - Folk, Classic music posters, 1970-2006 (Folder 88-90)
  - Classic music posters, 1970-2006 (Folder 91)
- Other, 1970-2006
  - Erotic posters, 1970-2006 (Folder 124-135)
  - Sex film posters 1-3, 1960-1970 (Folder 136-138)
    The ones by Constantin Film are dated in the code on bottom margin of poster.
  - Sex film posters 1-3, 1960-1970 (Folder 139-141)
  - Mostly album/CD release posters, 1970-2006 (Folder 103-107)
  - Mostly album/CD promotion posters, 1970-2006 (Folder 108-119)
  - Kraftwerk's Autobahn poster, 1970-2006 (Folder 122)